serversea.com 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Server Sea Hosting Company

ServerSea has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: ServerSea.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

This site contains links to other sites. ServerSea is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are or may be collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Changes to this Policy**

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy will be kept in an archive for you to view.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [sales@serversea.com](mailto:sales@serversea.com)
